In this American English pronunciation video, we're going to go over how to pronounce the IH as in SIT vowel.
在这段美式英语发音视频中，我们将学习如何发音像SIT中的IH元音。
This vowel can be a challenge for non-native speakers.
对于非母语者来说，这个元音可能是一个挑战。
The tendency is to replace it with the EE vowel, but for the IH vowel, the jaw drops more, so the tongue isn't as close to the roof of the mouth.
人们倾向于用EE元音来替代它，但对于IH元音，下巴要放得更低，因此舌头不会靠近上颚。
Let's study the mouth position.
让我们研究一下口腔的位置。
There's a relaxed jaw drop.
下巴自然放松下垂。
The tip of the tongue stays forward, lightly touching the back of the bottom front teeth.
舌尖保持向前，轻轻触碰下前牙的后面。
The top, front part of the tongue arches up towards the roof of the mouth.
舌头的前上部分向上拱起，靠近上颚。
Let's see this vowel up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察这个元音。
Relaxed jaw drop.
放松的下巴下垂。
Tongue tip forward.
舌尖向前。
Top, front part of the tongue arches up towards the roof of the mouth.
舌头的前上部分向上拱起，靠近上颚。
This vowel is stressed in the word FIX.
这个元音在单词FIX中是重读的。
Same mouth position.
相同的口腔位置。
When this vowel is in a stressed word or syllable, like FIX, it has an up-down shape.
当这个元音在重读的单词或音节中时，比如FIX，它有一个上升-下降的形状。
IH, FIX, IH.
When it's in an unstressed syllable, it will be flatter and lower in pitch, quieter.
当它在非重读音节中时，音调会更平、更低、更安静。
IH, IH.
It's unstressed in the word OFFICE.
在单词OFFICE中是非重读的。
IH.
The mouth position is the same, but a little more relaxed.
口腔位置相同，但稍微更放松。
Let's compare the stressed IH in FIX, on top, to the unstressed IH in OFFICE.
让我们比较一下FIX中重读的IH和OFFICE中非重读的IH。
Notice that the jaw is more dropped for the stressed syllable.
注意在重读音节中下巴放得更低。
For the unstressed IH, the jaw is less dropped.
对于非重读的IH，下巴放得较少。
This is typical.
这是典型的。
Unstressed vowels are shorter, so there isn't as much time to make the full mouth position.
非重读元音更短，所以没有那么多时间来完成完整的口腔位置。
Stressed IH.
重读的IH。
Fix.
IH.
Unstressed IH.
非重读的IH。
Office.
IH.
IH, IH.
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Which.
IH.
Instead.
Begin.
IH.
Divorce.
Busy.
IH.
Print.